I'm enjoying doing the thumbnails I'm a
kangaroo I'm gonna have an English
probably that's probably a better face
but like I said I know a ranch is the
right word but I really love the idea of
a resource-based economy it's what I'm
trying my whole concept of the tech
company is helping get there in a
voluntary actual way instead of like the
whole world that's all simultaneously
agree to this and then every broke down
but I get why they did that and honestly
coming from that is a big reason why
I've got any ideas I have but one of my
biggest issues with the zeitgeist
movement is they're anti religious
stance cuz it's not like yeah pretty
much it's hurting us it's like yeah I
don't know like it comes off as its own
religion like its own belief system that
like this is the only one you have to
have this way or no other it's like that
is religion like that is that's like
science does that too and they are doing
it in a scientific way I'm like can't we
have science like is the truth that we
all can agree on even if you don't agree
on it like the masses agree on it the
masses have done the like the work
together to say yes this is this is like
the statistics of probabilities and
everything like this is better science
and we're science and still allow people
to hold their religion and I asked I
posted on the website and is actually
asking like wait like this sounds like
you're taking religion away from people
as opposed to letting it following
naturally if that happens like I don't
know if the Vatican still exists when
they're not getting tides because
there's no money left right I don't even
know if we ever transitioned hurry based
on like that's my vision but when
something's a democracy it alters right
there might be three decks but I think I
don't know like it comes off as its own
religion and then it also puts off like
everyone who has any kind of
spirituality or religion you have to
like the only people it's like only the
science religion only the Darwin's fall
of Darwin's um other guy someone just
posted Dawkins the only Dawkins
followers are gonna be coming on board
I'm like no we need like I have so many
intelligent friends that are of every
different religion they don't require
that I follow it they don't require like
we can have a conversation
sation about anything and they're not
they might bring the religion into it
like this is what influence is it but
they're not gonna quote the Bible like
this is now law like it's like we have
to do this because it's law and I get
that many areas of the world that is
happening including our areas in the
world with the religious the far
religious right but just they're like
we'll just educate it out of them like
what if they don't get it like what if
they still hold true to it though like
what if it is still something they want
like if they want a place of worship and
they want their their own religious
texts why not like why is that a problem
that meeting everyone to have that are
committing acts of violence to make that
happen
definitely not okay but having a
religion having spiritual having a group
of people who believe in something that
is that is common I don't think that
that gets educated out in fact I think
we just find that but in more niche ways
like I'm like I don't want to say you
can't have religion I help you find your
religious spiritual community so that
you get like if if they have a monopoly
on your life and religion if you're it's
the only church that you feel like you
can be a part of you're going to toe the
line more than if you're like yeah you
guys are anti-gay I'm not I'm gonna go
find a church that is right and in
Christianity in the West you can find
that because it's like there's so much
diversity in Christianity that you can
find what values you hold you might have
to leave your family but you're not you
could still find your spiritual
community
I don't think saying no there's no
religion because then it's going to be
under the radar and it's going to be
like people can't talk about it so they
can't find their true people and then
therefore have real conversations that
help them evolve either beyond religion
if that's what their path is or holding
true to it and I just think it's like
hurting the entire movement because and
this conversation was very much old I
was like I don't think you understand or
try it like people here you're gonna
take their religion way instead of it's
going to naturally fall off and they are
more or less like oh yeah we were gonna
take it away with religion with
education taking it away what happens if
they're still religious what happen on
educate people out of that like you just
you can't you have to meet them where
they are
and allow them to be there not require
them to get somewhere like you need
there the world's never gonna get to
what they're just funny because I have
this whole vision but the more but I'm
like I'd like the more I let go of that
but still like hold it I don't know what
if the word is even like lightly like no
there's reasons it's that way but like
hold space for it but still allow other
input and allow I'm like no other people
don't want it like this they want it
like that and allowing more room for
diversity where it's not I give my way
so they get their way it's like how can
we all have our way how can we all have
spiritual communities if that's what we
want or not if that's what we want and
still have truth and science is like our
fundamental the thing we all can kind of
come back to together